William Arasirwa: lakini i need lessons on presentation
Stanley Njihia: Mnaskia reverb wakubwa
William Arasirwa: eeeeh
Stanley Njihia: Peris, cheza na massgrave io watermark iko apo bottom right iache kukusumbua.
William Arasirwa: address the elephant in the room
William Arasirwa: watu wa car dataset tuliona vumb
Stanley Njihia: ptsd
Stanley Njihia: lakini ii maneno ingesaidia sana io time.
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: unabreathe
Stanley Njihia: Yani TM amesema sisi wengine tuko na mchezo
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: ana pumua
Fridah Njung'e: stenographer
William Arasirwa: ann and jeff mnaona kazi yenu
Norman Mwapea: Mr who now?
Judith Otieno: Hatakuwa the blacksheep, not Mr. Blacksheep
Fridah Njung'e: thought i heard Mr. Blackson
William Arasirwa: car crashes was diabolical work
Stanley Njihia: 2 million rows 150 columns
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: after cleaning 1.3
Stanley Njihia: Mmeona TM akismile? Apa tutatii.
Kitts Kikumu: rel btwn features
Fridah Njung'e: multiple colinearity between features
Fridah Njung'e: corelation i mean
Huldah Rotich: when more than two independent variables (features) are correlated
Norman Mwapea: Ile ya features predicting features
William Arasirwa: we have more than one year right?
William Arasirwa: lakini ata waafrika hawangefikiria hivi
William Arasirwa: levels
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: more than one year for?
William Arasirwa: screams in anguish
Fridah Njung'e: crying in clusters
Jeff Mogaka: arasirwa applying clustering with his shawries
Jeff Mogaka: Ngaire clustering her diets
William Arasirwa: wewe kaa hapo na labda uko infertile
Alvin kipleting: wueeh
Leon Wairachu: 1:0
Jeff Mogaka: shit nafaa kuconfirm
William Arasirwa: na nani?
Stanley Njihia: foul confirmed
Alvin kipleting: na nani huyo
Jeff Mogaka: he dived ref he dived
William Arasirwa: ama sikuhizi mkono yako ya left ikona overies?
Stanley Njihia: aah
Leon Wairachu: VAR goal
Fridah Njung'e: jeff anaeza self pollinate
Alvin kipleting: @ann jeff anasema malizia website mbio mbio
Kitts Kikumu: Ati jeff ako infertile
Jeff Mogaka: @ann hiyo dating app naeza kua infertile
Alvin kipleting: its 2 :0 in the first 5 minutes
Jeff Mogaka: no he diuved ref
William Arasirwa: unashangaa mbona jeff akona mixed personalities, kumbe its estrogen levels fighting with testosterone and we all know who is the winner
Judith Otieno: Jeff tumekuekea multibet we need 2:3
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: @jeff helping the unfortunate is my passion
William Arasirwa: reasons why amesuka
William Arasirwa: anyway
Stacy Mogeni: self love muhimu
Kitts Kikumu: lol
William Arasirwa: self love na anajikamua libido?
Jeff Mogaka: @Judith unassema umeeka correct score ya 2:3
Leon Wairachu: 3:0
Stanley Njihia: Arasirwa umesema uyo ni hermaphrodite
Norman Mwapea: Stanley, slef love... kujibaka doesnt qualify, right?
William Arasirwa: allegedly
Jeff Mogaka: @stacy damn
Alvin kipleting: judith anasema tumeeekelea gg and over2.5
William Arasirwa: lakini mbona uspank ukuta @jeff
Norman Mwapea: Oh sio stanley. Stacy
Norman Mwapea: Na anamoan jinalake
Leon Wairachu: It has now become a game of men against boys
4:0
Mercy Kirwa: Waah!
William Arasirwa: na unaishi kwa bedsitter, orgasm moja umeangukia vyombbo
Stanley Njihia: Eeiiyy
Jeff Mogaka: mnashuka tu na mm damn
Fridah Njung'e: anajibaka anajiita babe
William Arasirwa: ei
Jeff Mogaka: acha ninawe mkono
Jeff Mogaka: this is just dirty stuff hell no
Leon Wairachu: haltime bana. Wacha apumue
William Arasirwa: cleanliness is key ya lef ama right?
Fridah Njung'e: wacha aende halftime kidogo...he needs to clap his cheeks
William Arasirwa: unashangaa jeff amenyamaza kumbe ako foreplay anajishika shingo kama plumber
Alvin kipleting: @ hii class iko level moja na peacemaker plus the boys
Jeff Mogaka: yooooooh
Norman Mwapea: Ati clap his cheeks
Leon Wairachu: wueeh Jeff forfeit
Nesphory Mwadime: Damn!
Jeff Mogaka: wueeeeh
Jeff Mogaka: wueeeh
Jeff Mogaka: hapa sitoboi
Stanley Njihia: Fridah, kanyaga that self loving mofo
Stacy Mogeni: tunaambiwa clap for group 5 yeye anaclap cheeks
Jeff Mogaka: even you stacy
William Arasirwa: then proceeds to pull his hair saying he is the price
Norman Mwapea: "Pull my hair"
Stanley Njihia: pull his own hair
Nesphory Mwadime: Sasa vile huyu ni mkisii, na tunajua wako na ndizi... ama wacha tu
Fridah Njung'e: akiwa in that new style,,,volkswagen
Jeff Mogaka: tulieni before Ngaire ajoin
William Arasirwa: mnadhani ni sound effects za anime kumbe ni jeff
Jeff Mogaka: halftime
Kitts Kikumu: 5:0 (45+3')
Alvin kipleting: @ jeff what did you do to make them niggas mad
Jeff Mogaka: @alvo I think ni just existing
Fridah Njung'e: chill girl...we just getting started....don't pout
Alvin kipleting: sahii unajiambia what did i do
William Arasirwa: lakini mbona uspank chupa ya lotion?
Fridah Njung'e: he bit more than he can chew @ alvin
Alvin kipleting: wahh
Jeff Mogaka: nitaongea phase 5
Fridah Njung'e: @arasirwa....anaspank ndio walie pamoja...
Jeff Mogaka: ama nichape comeback hii halftime
William Arasirwa: unapata jeff amejitandaza kama Cartesian plane kumbe he is plotting his next satisfaction
William Arasirwa: anyway
Jeff Mogaka: si wewe Fridah ulikua unalia ju ya JONTE phase 1
William Arasirwa: **cumback
William Arasirwa: thats not my handwriting
Alvin kipleting: @ jeff sidhani comeback itamake ,nani huyo amesema jeff anatumia roll on
Jeff Mogaka: like your fatherless gf who planned her escape from you
Fridah Njung'e: sasa mambo ya phase 1 na tuko karibu kugraduate...kwani your *cumbacks are getting how old
Jeff Mogaka: @alvo eii bana
Leon Wairachu: Own goal
William Arasirwa: then you call yourself daddy, unlike my fatherless girlfreind
Jeff Mogaka: i give up
Jeff Mogaka: you win
William Arasirwa: bro is busy testing his gag reflex on himself
Jeff Mogaka: mmeshinda acha tuelewe dendogram
William Arasirwa: juu zinakaa chupa ya lotion sio
Fridah Njung'e: @jeff...you wanna climb the decision tree??
Norman Mwapea: Testing the gag reflex is nasty nasty stuff
Jeff Mogaka: maguys I'm straight
William Arasirwa: climb what? damn
Fridah Njung'e: as a roundabout
Jeff Mogaka: mnaoverdo man
William Arasirwa: like your left hand?
Nesphory Mwadime: Juu Alice is the name of your right hand ama?
William Arasirwa: that was a rough tackle
Jeff Mogaka: eishh
Alvin kipleting: jeff nikama itabidi nimeorganize a boxing match
Jeff Mogaka: hii graduation nakuja na gun tutaona nani atcheka then
William Arasirwa: atleast you will have a shot
Fridah Njung'e: from today we refer to jeff as Quagmire...agreed?
Alvin kipleting: eiii
Nesphory Mwadime: Alafu ziwe blank
William Arasirwa: damn
Jeff Mogaka: wueeeeh
Jeff Mogaka: eh eh eh sniffs mbake
Norman Mwapea: Hii si ni ile table ya fare
Fridah Njung'e: mm naona tu p2 labda nipee jeff iongezee hormones
Jeff Mogaka: hizi data points zinakaa networth ya fridha
Kitts Kikumu: offside
Fridah Njung'e: can't even spell my name straight
William Arasirwa: jeff is trying to make a comeback late in the game
Jeff Mogaka: mm si kaa team yako
Fridah Njung'e: jeff ni ule goalkeeper mpya wa man u...just strutting in the field
William Arasirwa: no wonder you glaze man city kumbe ukona kink ya pep
Jeff Mogaka: kaa vile love life yako ina struff at Fridah
William Arasirwa: offside
Jeff Mogaka: huyu mwingine wa pickup
Leon Wairachu: Mogaka akaona Nunez kama striker
Jeff Mogaka: shots off target
William Arasirwa: nicolas jackson
Jeff Mogaka: nikama nachapa own goals chini ya maji
Jeff Mogaka: acha tu nijisub
Leon Wairachu: Na Onana
William Arasirwa: effects of making yourself wet, chini ya maji for a reason
Jeff Mogaka: hizo tricks zako na Norman mm sijui
Fridah Njung'e: jeff go sit at the kids table....the adults need to decide what to do with you...na usijibake while at it
Alvin kipleting: @ jeff venye unakuwa battered is a good example of how villains are made
Jeff Mogaka: true very true...nashindana na millenials nilisahau
Jeff Mogaka: @alvo leo usiku naingia villain arch yangu
Fridah Njung'e: your age shouldn't justify you being daft
Jeff Mogaka: nitatokwa na uwazimu
William Arasirwa: villan arch ama unapractice kuarch your back?
Alvin kipleting: wuehh
Stanley Njihia: Alvin, uyo ata akakua villain labda akue plankton
Fridah Njung'e: shots fired....downward dog position activated
Jeff Mogaka: hizi styles zako ficha bana
Norman Mwapea: Mwenye ata analyse chat ya leo atawika
Jeff Mogaka: heeeh
Jeff Mogaka: hizi ndio ulikua unasetia Jonte before akuache
Jeff Mogaka: ju ni haikuwork
Fridah Njung'e: si ni ww na yoga styles zako...activating your inner chi...ama ni chick?
William Arasirwa: wuh
Alvin kipleting: ghaii
William Arasirwa: wueh
William Arasirwa: relax guys
William Arasirwa: anytime jeff comes up, he goes down
William Arasirwa: where is maureen??
Jeff Mogaka: arasirwa tulia
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: brain imejaa
William Arasirwa: that was cold though
Jeff Mogaka: wuii leo nimetii ajab
William Arasirwa: @norman msidie huyu
Fridah Njung'e: norman will kill him
William Arasirwa: kwani tunafanya electronics
Stanley Njihia: Hadi 4pm Ann, he's just warming up.
Fridah Njung'e: zinakaa circuits sio?
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: my laptop
Kitts Kikumu: ann speaker ishaanza
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: i cant talk
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: na laptop imechoka
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: also hiyo kitu
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: the gram
Leon Wairachu: Leo umeinject
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: ni diani.?
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: diana?
William Arasirwa: is jeff breathing?
Fridah Njung'e: karibu amalize arudi...chill
Nesphory Mwadime: He is probably moaning to himself
William Arasirwa: gai
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: arasirwa
Kitts Kikumu: diana is divisive, its the opposite of agnes. Ama tumuulize @ann
William Arasirwa: mwenye atafanya analysis ya hii chat leo ataona moto
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: scifi
Alvin kipleting: @ jeff ndio aura irudi naona itabidi umetumia OSINT on some people here
Fridah Njung'e: anamedidate na happy pink thoughts..flowers and fluff
Stanley Njihia: confirmed
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: explain your profession to a 8 year old
Fridah Njung'e: @felicity ME to child...leo tunachongoa jeff...go wild child
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: @ chat mumefukuza jeff
Fridah Njung'e: he's probably crying...one should check on him
Jeff Mogaka: @nn hawa hawaezi nishtua
Stanley Njihia: Naskia wamesema ati ako moaning
Fridah Njung'e: waaaaah
Jeff Mogaka: stanley ni wewe unasema
Jeff Mogaka: si ati nimeskia
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: pretty
Jeff Mogaka: watch your back nitakuamulia one day
Fridah Njung'e: utamspank ama
William Arasirwa: wueh
Jeff Mogaka: zii jiulize kwann Ngaire sikuhizi ako humble
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: stan jeff is coming for you
Nesphory Mwadime: Unamwambia not to drop the soap?
Jeff Mogaka: infack wewe ni next
Alvin kipleting: rada nes
Kelvin Kinoti: Can you send this r script at mattermost too
Jeff Mogaka: Nea bana
Fridah Njung'e: ata akidrop kila kitu bado jeff atashindwa
William Arasirwa: yall getting zesty eey
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: somebody ask him about the one he mentioned called jack or sthg
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: the tm i mean
William Arasirwa: wewe na wewe nunua mic
Fridah Njung'e: mic yake imeraruka.....
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: laptop is tired needs to reboot
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: someone ask
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: eheeeee basssssssssss
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: and jack
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: python r and jack
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: gani mzuri
Fridah Njung'e: r is better
Fridah Njung'e: than python i guess
Leon Wairachu: better in terms of?
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: overall dsc
Fridah Njung'e: not sure...phase 0 tm said that
Alvin kipleting: @ norman ulimention umaps hiyo inatumika wapi
Norman Mwapea: In visualizing clusters
William Okomba: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tXYAdGn-SuM
Norman Mwapea: They're basically scatter plots but for clusters
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: kesho tunado?
William Arasirwa: the week is long
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: this month
William Arasirwa: jeff smiling when he hears deep learning
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: ati before real project
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: kwaaaaaaani???
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: tunafanya tu fake ?
Stanley Njihia: aviator
Norman Mwapea: time series is so cool
Leon Wairachu: Mogaka